Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Files 5623
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Subject Files - A-C (Box 5)
  - J.E. Christman Injury, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    February 1, 1968
  - Circular of Instructions, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Circular of Instructions - 1957 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Circular of Instructions - 1958 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Circular of Instructions - 1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Clippings - 1954 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Circular of Instructions - 1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Circular of Instructions - 1961 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Circular of Instructions - 1962 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Close Clearance - 1952 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - C.P. Collins, Secy. Legis. Board (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Committee to Free Earl Browder (H.T. Elder Lodge 90) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Conferences - Representatives other railroad brotherhoods (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - CONSOLIDATION - Order Ry Conductors and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - Legislators (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Expenses - 1962 W.E.B Chase, G.S. and T (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - G.S. & Y W.E.B. Chase, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - W.B. Chase - General Secretary and Treasurer - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - General Correspondence - W.E.B. Chase - G.S. & T, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - W.P. Kennedy, President General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - W.P. Kennedy, President General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - W.P. Kennedy - President, B of R.T. General Correspondence, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Subject Files - C-Leg (Box 6)
  - W.P. Kennedy, President - General Correspondence 1957 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - W.P. Kennedy, President - General Correspondence 1958 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy, President - General Correspondence 1955 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - W.P. Kennedy President, BRT - General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - W.J. Weil - General Secretary and Treasurer, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - W.J. Weil - General Secretary & Treasurer - General Correspondence 1958 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1962 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Credentials - 1960 Reorganization Meeting (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Delaware and Hudson RR - Loree Plan 1934 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Department of Health - Quality of Ware at B&O RR - Brooks Avenue, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    April 24, 1973
  - Governor Thomas E. Dewey (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Discrimination 1945 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Elimination Grade Crossings 1938 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - ICC #16436 - Erie - Lackawanna RR (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Erie Railroad Company Claim of Yard Brakeman C.P. Kerwin Award No. 4660 Docket No. 6688 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Erwin Travia Bills Amending Election Law for regulation for political expenditures & assessments by unincorporated Associations., etc. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Expense Bill -1961 W.B. E.B. Chase, G.S. & T. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Federal Legislation - Train Brake Bill - H.R. 5124 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Federal Legislation 1947 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Federal Legislation - Joint Resolution Compulsory Retirement - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Federal - Senate Bill S. 3097 Merger Moratorium (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Federal - S 3216 - Repeal Sec. 13 Transportation Act (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Federal Legislation - Power or Train Brake Bill Locomotive Inspection Act Amendments Hours of Service Act Amendments - Railroad Retirements Amendments (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Federal Legislation - Installation, Inspection, Maintenance, and repair of Power or Train Brakes by ICC (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Federal Legislation RE: H.R. 1889 - "Railroad Car Inspection Act of 1959" (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Federal Legislation S. 3044 HR 10864 - An act to facilitate pipe line construction to transport coal slurry (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Financial Statement Legis. Bd. 1913 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - John Fitzgibbons - files on campaign for Congress (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - General Chairmen Erie Railroad System (F.J. Moran, GC) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - General Chairmen Erie Railroad System (C.S. Rosser, GC) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - General Chairmen - New York Central, Lines East H.A. Johnson, GC (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - General Chairmen New York Central, Lines East H.A. Johnson, GC (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Grade Crossings, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Grade Crossings 1946 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Governor Averell Harriman (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Governor Averell Harriman - General 1957-8, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Hours of Service - Bus and Trucks, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Hours of Service - Truck & Bus Drivers, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - I.C.C. Service Orders 843 and 845 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Hours of Service - Bus and Truck Drivers 1937 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Insurance Circulars (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Insurance Law - Fraternal Societies, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Interstate Association of Local Chairmen of New York Harbor Switching District No. 5, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Interstate Ass'n of Local Committees New York Harbor Switching District (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Interstate Ass'n of Local Committees New York Harbor Switching District No. 5 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Ladies' Auxiliary TO B. of R.T. - General Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Ladies' Auxiliary 1961 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Ladies Auxiliary 1962 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Legal Aid Department (Interpretation W.C. Law LS & Harb Workers Act Federal Employers' Liability Act) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Legislation - 1953 - Weekly Pay Bill (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Legis. RAPP Bills - 1934 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Legis. Bd. Appt C.H. Sullivan St. Legis. Repr., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Legislative Board Correspondence 1962 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Reorganization Legis. Board, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Subject Files - Leg-Pol (Box 7)
  - Reorganization Board 1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Reorganization Legis. Board 1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Legis. Bd. Salary & Per Diem 1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1952 - Reorganization Meeting - New York State Legislative Board (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Reorganization New York Legislative board 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Long Island Railroad Legislation 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Long Island Railroad 1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - E.A. Martin - Vice Chairman, Legis. Board 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Report (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Monthly Report, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - National Conference of State Legislative Representatives, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - National Conference Legislative Representatives - Minutes 1925-1929-1930-1932, 1929-1932 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - National Conference of State Legislative Representatives General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - National Legislative Representative Harry See, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - National Legislative Representative (Harry See), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - National Conference (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - National Legislative Representative (Harry See) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - National Legislative Representative (Harry See) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Harry See - National Legislative Representative, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - National Wage Movements - Increases In Pay (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - National Wage Movement -1961 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - National Wage Movement 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - New York State Disability Benefits Law (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - New York State Legislative Board - General, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - New York State Legislative Board (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - State School of Industrial Labor Relations (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - State School of Industrial Labor Relations 1952 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - NY State School Industrial Labor Relations 1947 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Niagara Frontier Local Chairmen's Ass'n (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Niagara Frontier Local Chairmen's Ass'n, 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Niagara Development Act of 1956 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - SPECIAL - Pertaining to 1958 Convention (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Political Activity 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Political Activity 1938 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Political - Public Relations - 1952 Correspondence, Roll Calls, Etc. (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Subject Files - Pol-State (Box 8)
  - Political Endorsements 1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Political General 1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Political Endorsements 1962 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Political - Public Relations - 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Political, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Political - Public Relations - General File, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Political - Correspondence with Members of Legislature (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Political - Public Relations - General File, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Political - Public Relations - 1954 - General File (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Platform Committee Material - 1962 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Political File 1962 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Political Information (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Political - Public Relations - 1951 - Correspondence, Roll Calls, Etc. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Political Action (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Political Action 1943 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Political Action 1944 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Political Action 1945 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Political Action 1946 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Political Action 1947 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Political Action 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Political Action 1949 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Re: Postponement of Natl Convention (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Proposed Passenger Train Service Act of 1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Railroad Frontiersmen of America, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Railroad Retirement Act Passed by the 82nd Congress (H.R.) 3669 Repr. Rodgers' Report on Railroad Retirement Amendments (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller - General (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller 1961 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Routine Resolutions 1960 Reorganizations Meeting (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Resolutions - 1960 Reorganization Meeting (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - "Right to Work" file (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller - 1962 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Special Circulars - 1959 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Special Circulars, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Special Circulars, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Special Circulars o instruction, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Misc. State Legislation for 1951 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - State Legislation 30 Day Bill, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - State Legislation - Close Clearance, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - State Legislation - Year 1950 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - State Legislation - 1950 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Subject Files - State-W (Box 9)
  - State Legislative Board - General 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - State Legislation - Close Clearance Bill (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Legislation - State Correspondence re Ins. Bills and other Bills (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - C.H. Sullivan - Personal General (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - C.H. Sullivan - Personal (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Sunday and Holiday Bill - Truck Legislation 1939 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Switchman's Union of NA (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Tolls on Canals 1938 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Trainman News (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Train Cancellations by Penn-Central Co., Inc. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Truck Legislation 1937 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Truck Legislation 1938 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Unification of RRs Metropolitan area 1939 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Special Convention File (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Truck Legislation 1951 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - U.R.O.C. (Box 9, Folder 16)